/***********************************************************************************************************************
 
* DISCLAIMER
 
* This software is supplied by Renesas Electronics Corporation and is only intended for use with Renesas products. No
 
* other uses are authorized. This software is owned by Renesas Electronics Corporation and is protected under all
 
* applicable laws, including copyright laws.
 
* THIS SOFTWARE IS PROVIDED "AS IS" AND RENESAS MAKES NO WARRANTIES REGARDING
 
* THIS SOFTWARE, WHETHER EXPRESS, IMPLIED OR STATUTORY, INCLUDING BUT NOT LIMITED TO WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY,
 
* FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE AND NON-INFRINGEMENT. ALL SUCH WARRANTIES ARE EXPRESSLY DISCLAIMED. TO THE MAXIMUM
 
* EXTENT PERMITTED NOT PROHIBITED BY LAW, NEITHER RENESAS ELECTRONICS CORPORATION NOR ANY OF ITS AFFILIATED COMPANIES
 
* SHALL BE LIABLE FOR ANY DIRECT, INDIRECT, SPECIAL, INCIDENTAL OR CONSEQUENTIAL DAMAGES FOR ANY REASON RELATED TO THIS
 
* SOFTWARE, EVEN IF RENESAS OR ITS AFFILIATES HAVE BEEN ADVISED OF THE POSSIBILITY OF SUCH DAMAGES.
 
* Renesas reserves the right, without notice, to make changes to this software and to discontinue the availability of
 
* this software. By using this software, you agree to the additional terms and conditions found by accessing the
 
* following link:
 
* http://www.renesas.com/disclaimer
 
*
 
* Copyright (C) 2019 Renesas Electronics Corporation. All rights reserved.
 ***********************************************************************************************************************/


1. Project Overview:

The example project demonstrates the typical use of the FLASH_HP HAL module APIs. The example project
   demonstrate the code flash 
and data flash operations once user provides the RTT input from the available commands list. 
   To exit from the demo user should 
choose the EXIT option.



NOTE  : User is expected to enter data of size not exceeding 15 bytes.
Operation is not guaranteed for any user input value other than integer(i.e. float, char, special char) through RTT.
