/***********************************************************************************************************************
* Copyright [2019] Renesas Electronics Corporation and/or its affiliates.  All Rights Reserved.
*
* This software is supplied by Renesas Electronics America Inc. and may only be used with products of Renesas Electronics Corp.
* and its affiliates (“Renesas”).  No other uses are authorized.  This software is protected under all applicable laws, 
* including copyright laws.
* Renesas reserves the right to change or discontinue this software.
* THE SOFTWARE IS DELIVERED TO YOU “AS IS,” AND RENESAS MAKES NO REPRESENTATIONS OR WARRANTIES, AND TO THE FULLEST EXTENT 
* PERMISSIBLE UNDER APPLICABLE LAW,DISCLAIMS ALL WARRANTIES, WHETHER EXPLICITLY OR IMPLICITLY, INCLUDING WARRANTIES OF 
* MERCHANTABILITY, FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE, AND NONINFRINGEMENT, WITH RESPECT TO THE SOFTWARE.  TO THE MAXIMUM 
* EXTENT PERMITTED BY LAW, IN NO EVENT WILL RENESAS BE LIABLE TO YOU IN CONNECTION WITH THE SOFTWARE (OR ANY PERSON 
* OR ENTITY CLAIMING RIGHTS DERIVED FROM YOU) FOR ANY LOSS, DAMAGES, OR CLAIMS WHATSOEVER, INCLUDING, WITHOUT LIMITATION, 
* ANY DIRECT, CONSEQUENTIAL, SPECIAL, INDIRECT, PUNITIVE, OR INCIDENTAL DAMAGES;
* ANY LOST PROFITS, OTHER ECONOMIC DAMAGE, PROPERTY DAMAGE, OR PERSONAL INJURY; AND EVEN IF RENESAS HAS BEEN ADVISED OF 
* THE POSSIBILITY OF SUCH LOSS,DAMAGES, CLAIMS OR COSTS.
***********************************************************************************************************************/

1. Project Overview:


The example project demonstrates the typical use of the SSI HAL module APIs. The project transfers
sample audio data from source buffer to destination buffer by connecting Tx and Rx pins and compares the transferred
data of two buffers. The result of comparison will be displayed on RTT viewer.

Hardware Connections:

EK-RA4M1:
Connect  P405 <--> P406

EK-RA6M1:
Connect  P405 <--> P406

EK-RA6M2:
Connect  P405 <--> P406

EK-RA6M3:
Connect  P405 <--> P406

EK-RA6M3G:
Connect  P405 <--> P406

NOTE:
In EK-RA6M3 and EK-RA6M3G boards, P403(which is also connected to SSISCK) is connected to LED1.So, it will glow while running the SSI application.
