/***********************************************************************************************************************
* 
* Copyright [2020] Renesas Electronics Corporation and/or its affiliates.  All Rights Reserved.
*
* This software is supplied by Renesas Electronics America Inc. and may only be used with products of Renesas Electronics Corp.
* and its affiliates (“Renesas”).  No other uses are authorized.  This software is protected under all applicable laws, 
* including copyright laws.
* Renesas reserves the right to change or discontinue this software.
* THE SOFTWARE IS DELIVERED TO YOU “AS IS,” AND RENESAS MAKES NO REPRESENTATIONS OR WARRANTIES, AND TO THE FULLEST EXTENT 
* PERMISSIBLE UNDER APPLICABLE LAW,DISCLAIMS ALL WARRANTIES, WHETHER EXPLICITLY OR IMPLICITLY, INCLUDING WARRANTIES OF 
* MERCHANTABILITY, FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE, AND NONINFRINGEMENT, WITH RESPECT TO THE SOFTWARE.  TO THE MAXIMUM 
* EXTENT PERMITTED BY LAW, IN NO EVENT WILL RENESAS BE LIABLE TO YOU IN CONNECTION WITH THE SOFTWARE (OR ANY PERSON 
* OR ENTITY CLAIMING RIGHTS DERIVED FROM YOU) FOR ANY LOSS, DAMAGES, OR CLAIMS WHATSOEVER, INCLUDING, WITHOUT LIMITATION, 
* ANY DIRECT, CONSEQUENTIAL, SPECIAL, INDIRECT, PUNITIVE, OR INCIDENTAL DAMAGES;
* ANY LOST PROFITS, OTHER ECONOMIC DAMAGE, PROPERTY DAMAGE, OR PERSONAL INJURY; AND EVEN IF RENESAS HAS BEEN ADVISED OF 
* THE POSSIBILITY OF SUCH LOSS,DAMAGES, CLAIMS OR COSTS.
* 
**********************************************************************************************************************/

1. Project Overview:

	This project demonstrates the basic functionality of AWS https client library with ethernet driver on Renesas RA MCUs 
based on Renesas FSP using FreeRTOS. aws client is used to connect to https adafruit server which is cloud platform. 
On successful connection, menu is displayed enabling user to send GET,PUT,POST requests to adafruit server. On POST/PUT 
request, MCU Die temperature is read via(using) ADC and uploaded to server. On GET request, the last MCU die temperature data 
is read from the adafruit server. JlinkRTTViewer is used to display the status and responses of the requests made to server.
  	

2. Hardware Requirement:

	i. micro usb cable - 1no.
       ii. LAN cable - 1no.
      iii. Ethernet Switch - 1no.

3. Hardware Connections:
 	Supported Board EK_RA6M3, EK_RA6M5:		
	i. Connect EK_RA6M3 board to Host machine using micro usb cable.
       ii. connect LAN cable on EK_RA6M3/EK_RA6M5 at ethernet port and other end connect to ethernet Switch. 
           Switch should have WAN connection to communicate the server over internet. The Switch should be connected to the router 
           which is connected to the Internet.
	
