/***********************************************************************************************************************
* Copyright [2020] Renesas Electronics Corporation and/or its affiliates.  All Rights Reserved.
*
* This software is supplied by Renesas Electronics America Inc. and may only be used with products of Renesas Electronics Corp.
* and its affiliates (“Renesas”).  No other uses are authorized.  This software is protected under all applicable laws, 
* including copyright laws.
* Renesas reserves the right to change or discontinue this software.
* THE SOFTWARE IS DELIVERED TO YOU “AS IS,” AND RENESAS MAKES NO REPRESENTATIONS OR WARRANTIES, AND TO THE FULLEST EXTENT 
* PERMISSIBLE UNDER APPLICABLE LAW,DISCLAIMS ALL WARRANTIES, WHETHER EXPLICITLY OR IMPLICITLY, INCLUDING WARRANTIES OF 
* MERCHANTABILITY, FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE, AND NONINFRINGEMENT, WITH RESPECT TO THE SOFTWARE.  TO THE MAXIMUM 
* EXTENT PERMITTED BY LAW, IN NO EVENT WILL RENESAS BE LIABLE TO YOU IN CONNECTION WITH THE SOFTWARE (OR ANY PERSON 
* OR ENTITY CLAIMING RIGHTS DERIVED FROM YOU) FOR ANY LOSS, DAMAGES, OR CLAIMS WHATSOEVER, INCLUDING, WITHOUT LIMITATION, 
* ANY DIRECT, CONSEQUENTIAL, SPECIAL, INDIRECT, PUNITIVE, OR INCIDENTAL DAMAGES;
* ANY LOST PROFITS, OTHER ECONOMIC DAMAGE, PROPERTY DAMAGE, OR PERSONAL INJURY; AND EVEN IF RENESAS HAS BEEN ADVISED OF 
* THE POSSIBILITY OF SUCH LOSS,DAMAGES, CLAIMS OR COSTS.
* **********************************************************************************************************************/

Project Overview:
    This example project demonstrates basic functionalities of USB Host Mass Storage Class (HMSC) driver
    with FreeRTOS+FAT file system on Renesas RA MCUs based on Renesas FSP. FreeRTOS+FAT uses the underlying
    Block media driver. The Block media driver utilizes USB HMSC driver to perform file operations on the
    USB storage devices. Error and info messages will be printed on JlinkRTTViewer.


Configuration changes to switch Speed in configurator: (same for EK-RA6M3 and EK-RA6M3G boards)

    High-Speed
        Setting USB module to be used  :    Using USB1 module
        USB Speed                      :    Hi Speed
        USB Module Number              :    USB_IP1 Port

    DMAC setting for High-Speed
    r_usb_basic stack:
        DMA support                  : Enable
        Transfer Source address      : Setting for HS module
        Transfer Destination address : Setting for HS module
    r_dmac stack for transfer and receive
        Transfer size(for both g_transfer0 & g_transfer1) : 4 Bytes
		Activation Source(for g_transfer0)      : USBHS FIFO 1(DMA transfer request 1)
        Activation Source(for g_transfer1)      : USBHS FIFO 0(DMA transfer request 0)

    Full-Speed (Default)
        Setting USB module to be used  :    Using USB0 module
        USB Speed                      :    Full Speed
        USB Module Number              :    USB_IP0 Port

    DMAC setting for Full-Speed (Default DMAC)
    r_usb_basic stack:
        DMA support                  : Enable
        Transfer Source address      : Setting for FS module
        Transfer Destination address : Setting for FS module
    r_dmac stack for transfer and receive
        Transfer size(for both g_transfer0 & g_transfer1) : 2 Bytes
		Activation Source(for g_transfer0)      : USBFS FIFO 1(DMA transfer request 1)
        Activation Source(for g_transfer1)      : USBFS FIFO 0(DMA transfer request 0)


Hardware Connections:
    High-Speed: (For EK-RA6M3/EK-RA6M3G only)
        Jumper j7: Connect pins 1-2
        Remove Jumper j17 pins
        Connect USB device to J6 connector with help of micro USB Host cable.

    Full-Speed:  (For EK-RA4M3/EK-RA6M3/EK-RA6M3G/EK-RA6M4/EK-RA4M2/EK-RA6M5)
        Jumper j12 placement is pins 1-2
        Remove Jumper j15 pins
        Connect USB device to J11 connector with help of micro USB Host cable.

Note:
1. By default USB HMSC Example Project runs in Full-speed mode.
2. Format the USB drive(with FAT32 file system) before performing any operation.
3. Data written can also be manually verified in file ra_usb.txt.
4. User is expected to execute "safely_eject" option before removing USB else further file operations may fail and USB data
5  may get corrupted.
6. If USB is removed without "safely_eject" option, user is recommended to perform "safely_eject" and "initialise USB" commands
   in sequence. This will make sure no USB operations fails after unexpected removal of USB.
7. User is expected to enter RTT input data of size not exceeding 20 bytes.
8. Operation is not guaranteed for any user input value other than integer, char(i.e. float, special char) through
   JlinkRTTViewer input.
