/***********************************************************************************************************************
* Copyright [2020] Renesas Electronics Corporation and/or its affiliates.  All Rights Reserved.
*
* This software is supplied by Renesas Electronics America Inc. and may only be used with products of Renesas Electronics Corp.
* and its affiliates (“Renesas”).  No other uses are authorized.  This software is protected under all applicable laws, 
* including copyright laws.
* Renesas reserves the right to change or discontinue this software.
* THE SOFTWARE IS DELIVERED TO YOU “AS IS,” AND RENESAS MAKES NO REPRESENTATIONS OR WARRANTIES, AND TO THE FULLEST EXTENT 
* PERMISSIBLE UNDER APPLICABLE LAW,DISCLAIMS ALL WARRANTIES, WHETHER EXPLICITLY OR IMPLICITLY, INCLUDING WARRANTIES OF 
* MERCHANTABILITY, FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE, AND NONINFRINGEMENT, WITH RESPECT TO THE SOFTWARE.  TO THE MAXIMUM 
* EXTENT PERMITTED BY LAW, IN NO EVENT WILL RENESAS BE LIABLE TO YOU IN CONNECTION WITH THE SOFTWARE (OR ANY PERSON 
* OR ENTITY CLAIMING RIGHTS DERIVED FROM YOU) FOR ANY LOSS, DAMAGES, OR CLAIMS WHATSOEVER, INCLUDING, WITHOUT LIMITATION, 
* ANY DIRECT, CONSEQUENTIAL, SPECIAL, INDIRECT, PUNITIVE, OR INCIDENTAL DAMAGES;
* ANY LOST PROFITS, OTHER ECONOMIC DAMAGE, PROPERTY DAMAGE, OR PERSONAL INJURY; AND EVEN IF RENESAS HAS BEEN ADVISED OF 
* THE POSSIBILITY OF SUCH LOSS,DAMAGES, CLAIMS OR COSTS.
* **********************************************************************************************************************/

1. Project Overview:
        The example project demonstrates some features of C++ like class, contructors,destructor, members functions using ADC 
        module hal API's provided by FSP.ADC module is wrapped into a class.An ADC object of class type is instantiated and is 
        used to call respective member functions which initiates scan and stop(in case of continuous scan mode).Results 
        and status are displayed on the JLinkRTTViewer.

2. Hardware settings for the project:
        Hardware connections:

        RA2A1-EK:
        1)J2 Connector Pin no:36(AVSS0)--------> Pin no: 34(VREFLO) with Jumper or wire
        Note: No Hardware connections required for other EK boards.

3. Configuration Settings:
        The example project, by default, runs in continuous scan mode on the boards, with the exception on EK-RA2A1, EK-RA2L1, EK-RA4M3 and EK-RA4M1.
        In order to switch the scan mode, change the 'Mode' field of ADC Driver in the RA configurator to Single Scan.

Note: EK-RA2A1, EK-RA2L1, EK-RA4M3 and EK-RA4M1 supports only Single Scan mode.
	





 
