/***********************************************************************************************************************
* 
* Copyright [2020] Renesas Electronics Corporation and/or its affiliates.  All Rights Reserved.
*
* This software is supplied by Renesas Electronics America Inc. and may only be used with products of Renesas Electronics Corp.
* and its affiliates (“Renesas”).  No other uses are authorized.  This software is protected under all applicable laws, 
* including copyright laws.
* Renesas reserves the right to change or discontinue this software.
* THE SOFTWARE IS DELIVERED TO YOU “AS IS,” AND RENESAS MAKES NO REPRESENTATIONS OR WARRANTIES, AND TO THE FULLEST EXTENT 
* PERMISSIBLE UNDER APPLICABLE LAW,DISCLAIMS ALL WARRANTIES, WHETHER EXPLICITLY OR IMPLICITLY, INCLUDING WARRANTIES OF 
* MERCHANTABILITY, FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE, AND NONINFRINGEMENT, WITH RESPECT TO THE SOFTWARE.  TO THE MAXIMUM 
* EXTENT PERMITTED BY LAW, IN NO EVENT WILL RENESAS BE LIABLE TO YOU IN CONNECTION WITH THE SOFTWARE (OR ANY PERSON 
* OR ENTITY CLAIMING RIGHTS DERIVED FROM YOU) FOR ANY LOSS, DAMAGES, OR CLAIMS WHATSOEVER, INCLUDING, WITHOUT LIMITATION, 
* ANY DIRECT, CONSEQUENTIAL, SPECIAL, INDIRECT, PUNITIVE, OR INCIDENTAL DAMAGES;
* ANY LOST PROFITS, OTHER ECONOMIC DAMAGE, PROPERTY DAMAGE, OR PERSONAL INJURY; AND EVEN IF RENESAS HAS BEEN ADVISED OF 
* THE POSSIBILITY OF SUCH LOSS,DAMAGES, CLAIMS OR COSTS.
* 
**********************************************************************************************************************/

Project Overview:

This example project demonstrates basic functionalities of DMAC driver on Renesas RA MCUs based on Renesas FSP.
Project initializes 3 DMAC transfer instances. Upon successful initialization, a menu option is displayed.
On user input "1", AGT generates 100msec interrupt to trigger a transfer from the source buffer to port control
register for 60 times indicated by LED blinking for 60 times. On user input "2", 32 bit data gets transferred 
from GPT counter register to destination array and display destination array data on RTT viewer.On user input "3",
32 bit data gets transferred from predefined source array to port register(LED) and state of LED changes accordingly. 

Note: 
1. On starting or reseting the board, at times the dmac transfer operation takes more time. Due to this the led blinking 
frequency decreases/pauses. Please reset the board in that case, and it will run as expected. 
2. LED blinking pauses in-between and then continues on RA6M3 and RA6M3G.

﻿
1) Segger RTT block address may needed to download and observe EP operation using a hex file with RTT-Viewer.
   RTT Block address for hex file committed in repository are as follows:
   a. e2studio: 0x200001c4
   b. Keil:	0x20000128
   c. IAR: 0x2000035c
 
2) If an EP is modified, compiled, and downloaded please find the block address (for the variable in RAM called _SEGGER_RTT) 
   in .map file generated in the build configuration folder (Debug/Release).
