/***********************************************************************************************************************
* 
* Copyright [2020] Renesas Electronics Corporation and/or its affiliates.  All Rights Reserved.
*
* This software is supplied by Renesas Electronics America Inc. and may only be used with products of Renesas Electronics Corp.
* and its affiliates (“Renesas”).  No other uses are authorized.  This software is protected under all applicable laws, 
* including copyright laws.
* Renesas reserves the right to change or discontinue this software.
* THE SOFTWARE IS DELIVERED TO YOU “AS IS,” AND RENESAS MAKES NO REPRESENTATIONS OR WARRANTIES, AND TO THE FULLEST EXTENT 
* PERMISSIBLE UNDER APPLICABLE LAW,DISCLAIMS ALL WARRANTIES, WHETHER EXPLICITLY OR IMPLICITLY, INCLUDING WARRANTIES OF 
* MERCHANTABILITY, FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE, AND NONINFRINGEMENT, WITH RESPECT TO THE SOFTWARE.  TO THE MAXIMUM 
* EXTENT PERMITTED BY LAW, IN NO EVENT WILL RENESAS BE LIABLE TO YOU IN CONNECTION WITH THE SOFTWARE (OR ANY PERSON 
* OR ENTITY CLAIMING RIGHTS DERIVED FROM YOU) FOR ANY LOSS, DAMAGES, OR CLAIMS WHATSOEVER, INCLUDING, WITHOUT LIMITATION, 
* ANY DIRECT, CONSEQUENTIAL, SPECIAL, INDIRECT, PUNITIVE, OR INCIDENTAL DAMAGES;
* ANY LOST PROFITS, OTHER ECONOMIC DAMAGE, PROPERTY DAMAGE, OR PERSONAL INJURY; AND EVEN IF RENESAS HAS BEEN ADVISED OF 
* THE POSSIBILITY OF SUCH LOSS,DAMAGES, CLAIMS OR COSTS.
* 
**********************************************************************************************************************/

1. Project Overview:
     This Example Project demonstrates the basic usage of SCI_SPI driver.
     The project writes commands to the slave sensor and reads the temperature value using SCI_SPI bus configured as master .
     The temperature values are continuously printed on JLink RTT Viewer.

2. Hardware settings for the project:


        Hardware connections:

        EK_RA2A1:     
        Connect Temperature sensor(J1:1) to PMODB(J6:1)
 
        EK_RA4M1/ EK_RA6M1/ EK_RA6M2 :
        Connect Temperature sensor(J1:1) to PMODA(J5:1)
        
        EK_RA6M3/ EK_RA6M3G/EK_RA2L1:
        Connect Temperature sensor(J1:1) to PMOD1(J26:1)	


        EK_RA4M3, EK_RA4M2,EK_RA6M4 and EK_RA2E1:
        Connect Temperature sensor(J1:1) to PMOD2(J25:1)

	EK_RA6T1:
	Temperature sensor(J1:4) to P102
	Temperature sensor(J1:2) to P101
	Temperature sensor(J1:3) to P100
	Temperature sensor(J1:5) to GND
	Temperature sensor(J1:6) to Vcc
	Temperature sensor(J1:1) to P103
		

        Temperature sensor used: MAX31723
