/***********************************************************************************************************************
* 
* Copyright [2020] Renesas Electronics Corporation and/or its affiliates.  All Rights Reserved.
*
* This software is supplied by Renesas Electronics America Inc. and may only be used with products of Renesas Electronics Corp.
* and its affiliates (“Renesas”).  No other uses are authorized.  This software is protected under all applicable laws, 
* including copyright laws.
* Renesas reserves the right to change or discontinue this software.
* THE SOFTWARE IS DELIVERED TO YOU “AS IS,” AND RENESAS MAKES NO REPRESENTATIONS OR WARRANTIES, AND TO THE FULLEST EXTENT 
* PERMISSIBLE UNDER APPLICABLE LAW,DISCLAIMS ALL WARRANTIES, WHETHER EXPLICITLY OR IMPLICITLY, INCLUDING WARRANTIES OF 
* MERCHANTABILITY, FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE, AND NONINFRINGEMENT, WITH RESPECT TO THE SOFTWARE.  TO THE MAXIMUM 
* EXTENT PERMITTED BY LAW, IN NO EVENT WILL RENESAS BE LIABLE TO YOU IN CONNECTION WITH THE SOFTWARE (OR ANY PERSON 
* OR ENTITY CLAIMING RIGHTS DERIVED FROM YOU) FOR ANY LOSS, DAMAGES, OR CLAIMS WHATSOEVER, INCLUDING, WITHOUT LIMITATION, 
* ANY DIRECT, CONSEQUENTIAL, SPECIAL, INDIRECT, PUNITIVE, OR INCIDENTAL DAMAGES;
* ANY LOST PROFITS, OTHER ECONOMIC DAMAGE, PROPERTY DAMAGE, OR PERSONAL INJURY; AND EVEN IF RENESAS HAS BEEN ADVISED OF 
* THE POSSIBILITY OF SUCH LOSS,DAMAGES, CLAIMS OR COSTS.
* 
**********************************************************************************************************************/

1. Project Overview:

        This project demonstrates the basic functionality of NetX Duo HTTPS client with ethernet driver on 
        Renesas RA MCUs based on Renesas FSP using AzureRTOS. The EP uses the DHCP client to get the IP address 
        from the DHCP server. On successful receiving of IP address from DHCP server and resolving the IP address 
        for the Domain name for "Adafruit IO" using the DNS lookup, On successful completion of DNS lookup, 
        the success status and IP address are displayed. Now HTTP Client is created and started.
        HTTP GET/SET/PUT operations can be performed by the user using the Menu provided on JLink RTT Viewer Console.
        Error and info messages will be printed on Jlink RTTViewer.

2. Hardware Requirement:

	i. Micro USB cable - 1no.
       ii. Ethernet Cable CAT5/6 (LAN cable) - 1no.
      iii. Ethernet Switch to connect to the router or LAN(connected to Internet) - 1no.

3. Hardware Connections:
 	Supported Board EK_RA6M3, EK_RA6M4 and EK_RA6M5:		
	i. Connect EK_RA6M3 board(J10)/ EK_RA6M4 board(J10)/ EK_RA6M5 board(J10) to Host machine using micro USB cable.
       ii. Connect LAN cable to the Ethernet Port of EK-RA6M3 and other end to the Ethernet Port on the switch 
           or Router. Switch connecting to the router or router should have access to the internet.
	
﻿
1) Segger RTT block address may needed to download and observe EP operation using a hex file with RTT-Viewer.
   RTT Block address for hex file committed in repository are as follows:
   a. e2studio: 0x2000b2dc
   b. Keil: Not Available 
   c. IAR: Not Available
 
2) If an EP is modified, compiled, and downloaded please find the block address (for the variable in RAM called _SEGGER_RTT) 
   in .map file generated in the build configuration folder (Debug/Release).
