/***********************************************************************************************************************
* Copyright [2020] Renesas Electronics Corporation and/or its affiliates.  All Rights Reserved.
*
* This software is supplied by Renesas Electronics America Inc. and may only be used with products of Renesas Electronics Corp.
* and its affiliates (“Renesas”).  No other uses are authorized.  This software is protected under all applicable laws, 
* including copyright laws.
* Renesas reserves the right to change or discontinue this software.
* THE SOFTWARE IS DELIVERED TO YOU “AS IS,” AND RENESAS MAKES NO REPRESENTATIONS OR WARRANTIES, AND TO THE FULLEST EXTENT 
* PERMISSIBLE UNDER APPLICABLE LAW,DISCLAIMS ALL WARRANTIES, WHETHER EXPLICITLY OR IMPLICITLY, INCLUDING WARRANTIES OF 
* MERCHANTABILITY, FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE, AND NONINFRINGEMENT, WITH RESPECT TO THE SOFTWARE.  TO THE MAXIMUM 
* EXTENT PERMITTED BY LAW, IN NO EVENT WILL RENESAS BE LIABLE TO YOU IN CONNECTION WITH THE SOFTWARE (OR ANY PERSON 
* OR ENTITY CLAIMING RIGHTS DERIVED FROM YOU) FOR ANY LOSS, DAMAGES, OR CLAIMS WHATSOEVER, INCLUDING, WITHOUT LIMITATION, 
* ANY DIRECT, CONSEQUENTIAL, SPECIAL, INDIRECT, PUNITIVE, OR INCIDENTAL DAMAGES;
* ANY LOST PROFITS, OTHER ECONOMIC DAMAGE, PROPERTY DAMAGE, OR PERSONAL INJURY; AND EVEN IF RENESAS HAS BEEN ADVISED OF 
* THE POSSIBILITY OF SUCH LOSS,DAMAGES, CLAIMS OR COSTS.
* **********************************************************************************************************************/

1. Project Overview:

        The example project demonstrates the typical use of the KINT HAL module APIs using matrix keypad for 4 keys (2X2)(row, column).
        It utilizes two keymatrix channel masks(KINT pins) and two GPIOs which will be connected to keypad's columns and rows respectively.
        On press of each key (one at a time), Row and Column information for the key pressed will be displayed in JlinkRTTViewer.

2. Hardware settings for the project:

        Hardware : 4x4 Matrix Membrane Keypad(Optional)
        Hardware connections:
        EK_RA6M3, EK_RA6M3G, EK_RA6M2, EK_RA6M1, EK_R4M1:
        1) (KINT pin)P106 -> Any Column pin of keypad.
        2) (KINT pin)P107 -> Any Column different from above pin of keypad.
        3) (GPIO)P101     -> Any row pin of keypad.
        4) (GPIO)P102     -> Any other row pin of keypad.

        EK_RA2A1:
        1) (KINT pin)P304 -> Any Column pin of keypad.
        2) (KINT pin)P303 -> Any Column different from above pin of keypad.
        3) (GPIO)P301     -> Any row pin of keypad.
        4) (GPIO)P302     -> Any other row pin of keypad.

Note :
1. External pull down resistors (4.7 Kohm) should be connected to KINT pins
2. If matrix keypad is not available, Please connect the Jumper wires to pins as specified above for particular MCU 
   and short row pin with any of the KINT pin.This will lead to generate key-event.
   The generated key-event is detected and printed on RTTViewer.
