/***********************************************************************************************************************
* Copyright [2020] Renesas Electronics Corporation and/or its affiliates.  All Rights Reserved.
*
* This software is supplied by Renesas Electronics America Inc. and may only be used with products of Renesas Electronics Corp.
* and its affiliates (“Renesas”).  No other uses are authorized.  This software is protected under all applicable laws, 
* including copyright laws.
* Renesas reserves the right to change or discontinue this software.
* THE SOFTWARE IS DELIVERED TO YOU “AS IS,” AND RENESAS MAKES NO REPRESENTATIONS OR WARRANTIES, AND TO THE FULLEST EXTENT 
* PERMISSIBLE UNDER APPLICABLE LAW,DISCLAIMS ALL WARRANTIES, WHETHER EXPLICITLY OR IMPLICITLY, INCLUDING WARRANTIES OF 
* MERCHANTABILITY, FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE, AND NONINFRINGEMENT, WITH RESPECT TO THE SOFTWARE.  TO THE MAXIMUM 
* EXTENT PERMITTED BY LAW, IN NO EVENT WILL RENESAS BE LIABLE TO YOU IN CONNECTION WITH THE SOFTWARE (OR ANY PERSON 
* OR ENTITY CLAIMING RIGHTS DERIVED FROM YOU) FOR ANY LOSS, DAMAGES, OR CLAIMS WHATSOEVER, INCLUDING, WITHOUT LIMITATION, 
* ANY DIRECT, CONSEQUENTIAL, SPECIAL, INDIRECT, PUNITIVE, OR INCIDENTAL DAMAGES;
* ANY LOST PROFITS, OTHER ECONOMIC DAMAGE, PROPERTY DAMAGE, OR PERSONAL INJURY; AND EVEN IF RENESAS HAS BEEN ADVISED OF 
* THE POSSIBILITY OF SUCH LOSS,DAMAGES, CLAIMS OR COSTS.
* **********************************************************************************************************************/

1. Project Overview:
    The example project demonstrates typical use of the IIC slave HAL module APIs.
    The project initializes IIC slave and IIC master module with standard rate and is made interfaced with loop-back mechanism.
    It performs Slave read and write operation continuously once initialization is successful. On successful I2C transaction
    (6 bytes), Data transceived is compared. Led blinks on data match else it is turned ON as sign of failure.
    Output message for both corresponding slave operations is displayed on RTT Viewer. Any API/event failure message is also 
    displayed.

2. Hardware Settings:
    Two jumper wires are required to establish loop back connection along IIC lines within the board with pins as mentioned below.
    RA6M3_EK/RA6M3G_EK
    --------
    Channel 0 has been used by IIC slave and channel 2 been used by IIC master
    1) Slave IIC pins
        IIC0 P401  ----> SDA
        IIC0 P408  ----> SCL
    2) Master IIC pins
        IIC2 P511  ----> SDA
        IIC2 P512  ----> SCL

    RA6M2_EK
    --------
    Channel 0 has been used by IIC slave and channel 1 been used by IIC master.
    1) Slave IIC pins
        IIC0 P401  ----> SDA
        IIC0 P400  ----> SCL
    2) Master IIC pins
        IIC1 P206  ----> SDA
        IIC1 P100  ----> SCL

    RA6M1_EK
    --------
    Channel 0 has been used by IIC slave and channel 1 been used by IIC master.
    1) Slave IIC pins
        IIC0 P401  ----> SDA
        IIC0 P400  ----> SCL
    2) Master IIC pins
        IIC1 P101  ----> SDA
        IIC1 P100  ----> SCL

    RA4M1_EK
    --------
    Channel 0 has been used by IIC slave and channel 1 been used by IIC master.
    1) Slave IIC pins
        IIC0 P401  ----> SDA
        IIC0 P400  ----> SCL
    2) Master IIC pins
        IIC1 P206  ----> SDA
        IIC1 P100  ----> SCL

    RA2A1_EK
    --------
    1) Slave IIC pins
        IIC0 P401  ----> SDA
        IIC0 P000  ----> SCL
    2) Master IIC pins
        IIC1 P400  ----> SDA
        IIC1 P109  ----> SCL

    RA4W1_EK
    --------
    1) Slave IIC pins
        IIC0 P407  ----> SDA
        IIC0 P204  ----> SCL
    2) Master IIC pins
        IIC1 P206  ----> SDA
        IIC1 P205  ----> SCL

    RA6M4_EK
    --------
    1) Master IIC pins
        IIC0 P401  ----> SDA
        IIC0 P408  ----> SCL
    2) Slave IIC pins
        IIC1 P206  ----> SDA
        IIC1 P205  ----> SCL

    RA6T1_RSSK
    --------
    1) Master IIC pins
        IIC0 P401  ----> SDA
        IIC0 P400  ----> SCL
    2) Slave IIC pins
        IIC1 P101  ----> SDA
        IIC1 P100  ----> SCL

    RA2L1_EK
    --------
    1) Master IIC pins
        IIC1 P206  ----> SDA
        IIC1 P205  ----> SCL
    2) Slave IIC pins
        IIC0 P401  ----> SDA
        IIC0 P400  ----> SCL

    RA4M3_EK
    --------
    1) Master IIC pins
        IIC1 P511  ----> SDA
        IIC1 P512  ----> SCL
    2) Slave IIC pins
        IIC0 P401  ----> SDA
        IIC0 P408  ----> SCL

    RA4M2_EK
    --------
    1) Master IIC pins
        IIC1 P206  ----> SDA
        IIC1 P205  ----> SCL
    2) Slave IIC pins
        IIC0 P401  ----> SDA
        IIC0 P400  ----> SCL

Note:
    For the functioning of IIC Slave on all the boards except for EK-RA6M3/EK-RA6M3G, external pull up resistors of value
    3.9 or 4.7k ohms are required to be connected on I2C(SDA/SCL) lines.
﻿
1) Segger RTT block address may needed to download and observe EP operation using a hex file with RTT-Viewer.
   RTT Block address for hex file committed in repository are as follows:
   a. e2studio: 0x200008c0
   b. Keil:	0x20000008
   c. IAR: 0x20000268
 
2) If an EP is modified, compiled, and downloaded please find the block address (for the variable in RAM called _SEGGER_RTT) 
   in .map file generated in the build configuration folder (Debug/Release).
