/***********************************************************************************************************************
* 
* Copyright [2020] Renesas Electronics Corporation and/or its affiliates.  All Rights Reserved.
*
* This software is supplied by Renesas Electronics America Inc. and may only be used with products of Renesas Electronics Corp.
* and its affiliates (“Renesas”).  No other uses are authorized.  This software is protected under all applicable laws, 
* including copyright laws.
* Renesas reserves the right to change or discontinue this software.
* THE SOFTWARE IS DELIVERED TO YOU “AS IS,” AND RENESAS MAKES NO REPRESENTATIONS OR WARRANTIES, AND TO THE FULLEST EXTENT 
* PERMISSIBLE UNDER APPLICABLE LAW,DISCLAIMS ALL WARRANTIES, WHETHER EXPLICITLY OR IMPLICITLY, INCLUDING WARRANTIES OF 
* MERCHANTABILITY, FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE, AND NONINFRINGEMENT, WITH RESPECT TO THE SOFTWARE.  TO THE MAXIMUM 
* EXTENT PERMITTED BY LAW, IN NO EVENT WILL RENESAS BE LIABLE TO YOU IN CONNECTION WITH THE SOFTWARE (OR ANY PERSON 
* OR ENTITY CLAIMING RIGHTS DERIVED FROM YOU) FOR ANY LOSS, DAMAGES, OR CLAIMS WHATSOEVER, INCLUDING, WITHOUT LIMITATION, 
* ANY DIRECT, CONSEQUENTIAL, SPECIAL, INDIRECT, PUNITIVE, OR INCIDENTAL DAMAGES;
* ANY LOST PROFITS, OTHER ECONOMIC DAMAGE, PROPERTY DAMAGE, OR PERSONAL INJURY; AND EVEN IF RENESAS HAS BEEN ADVISED OF 
* THE POSSIBILITY OF SUCH LOSS,DAMAGES, CLAIMS OR COSTS.
* 
**********************************************************************************************************************/

1. Project Overview:
	 
	This project demonstrates the basic functionality of CAN module on Renesas RA MCUs using 2 RA boards.
	On pressing any key on the RTTViewer, data is transmitted from Board1 to Board2.
	On reception, Board2 displays the received data on the RTTViewer. Board2, then, transmits the
	framed data back to Board1. On successful transmission, Board1 prints the data on to the RTTViewer.

2. Hardware Connections:
       Require 2 CAN transceiver boards (Part# Waveshare SN65HVD230) and 2 RA boards to run the project

       Supported RA Boards: ek-ra4m2, ek-ra4m3, ek-ra6m1, ek-ra6m2, ek-ra6m3, ek-ra6m3g, ek-ra6m4, rssk-ra6t1
       (Please refer Note* for ek-ra4m2 and ek-ra4m3 pin connections) 
 
        CAN Transceiver Board1:
	   CANL:Transceiver Board 2 (CANL)
           CANH:Transceiver Board 2 (CANH)
	   CTX: P-401 (RA Board 1)
	   CRX: P-402 (RA Board 1)
	   3.3V: Vcc (RA Board 1)
	   GND: Vss/GND (RA Board 1)

        CAN Transceiver Board2:
	   CANL:Transceiver Board 1 (CANL)
	   CANH:Transceiver Board 1 (CANH)	 
	   CTX: P-401 (RA Board 2)
	   CRX: P-402 (RA Board 2)
	   3.3V: Vcc (RA Board 2)
	   GND: Vss/GND (RA Board 2)

*Note: On ek-ra4m2, configured channel:0 and pins are CTX:P-103 and CRX:P-102
       On ek-ra4m3, configured channel:1 and pins are CTX:P-609 and CRX:P-610
       ﻿
1) Segger RTT block address may needed to download and observe EP operation using a hex file with RTT-Viewer.
   RTT Block address for hex file committed in repository are as follows:
   a. e2studio: 0x200005f4
   b. Keil: Not Available 
   c. IAR: Not Available
 
2) If an EP is modified, compiled, and downloaded please find the block address (for the variable in RAM called _SEGGER_RTT) 
   in .map file generated in the build configuration folder (Debug/Release).
