/***********************************************************************************************************************
* 
* Copyright [2020] Renesas Electronics Corporation and/or its affiliates.  All Rights Reserved.
*
* This software is supplied by Renesas Electronics America Inc. and may only be used with products of Renesas Electronics Corp.
* and its affiliates (“Renesas”).  No other uses are authorized.  This software is protected under all applicable laws, 
* including copyright laws.
* Renesas reserves the right to change or discontinue this software.
* THE SOFTWARE IS DELIVERED TO YOU “AS IS,” AND RENESAS MAKES NO REPRESENTATIONS OR WARRANTIES, AND TO THE FULLEST EXTENT 
* PERMISSIBLE UNDER APPLICABLE LAW,DISCLAIMS ALL WARRANTIES, WHETHER EXPLICITLY OR IMPLICITLY, INCLUDING WARRANTIES OF 
* MERCHANTABILITY, FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE, AND NONINFRINGEMENT, WITH RESPECT TO THE SOFTWARE.  TO THE MAXIMUM 
* EXTENT PERMITTED BY LAW, IN NO EVENT WILL RENESAS BE LIABLE TO YOU IN CONNECTION WITH THE SOFTWARE (OR ANY PERSON 
* OR ENTITY CLAIMING RIGHTS DERIVED FROM YOU) FOR ANY LOSS, DAMAGES, OR CLAIMS WHATSOEVER, INCLUDING, WITHOUT LIMITATION, 
* ANY DIRECT, CONSEQUENTIAL, SPECIAL, INDIRECT, PUNITIVE, OR INCIDENTAL DAMAGES;
* ANY LOST PROFITS, OTHER ECONOMIC DAMAGE, PROPERTY DAMAGE, OR PERSONAL INJURY; AND EVEN IF RENESAS HAS BEEN ADVISED OF 
* THE POSSIBILITY OF SUCH LOSS,DAMAGES, CLAIMS OR COSTS.
* 
**********************************************************************************************************************/

1. Project Overview:
     The example project demonstrates the typical use of the SPI HAL module APIs.The project configure 
     SPI channels (Channel 0 and Channel 1) in Master and Slave mode.Once the module is initialised and the 
     channels are configured, Master and Slave can transmit and receive data based on commands from user sent through JLinkRTTViewer.

2. Hardware settings for the project:

        Hardware connections:
        
        Pin Connection for EK-RA2A1
	MISO  ----> P109 - P104
	MOSI  ----> P400 - P105
	RSPCK ----> P110 - P103
	
        Pin Connection for EK-RA4M1
	MISO  ----> P410 - P202
	MOSI  ----> P411 - P203
	RSPCK ----> P412 - P204

        Pin Connection for EK-RA6M1
	MISO  ----> P100 - P110
	MOSI  ----> P101 - P109
	RSPCK ----> P102 - P111

	Pin Connection for EK-RA6M2
	MISO  ----> P410 - P202
	MOSI  ----> P411 - P203
	RSPCK ----> P412 - P204

        Pin Connection for EK-RA6M3
        MISO  ----> P410 - P202
	MOSI  ----> P411 - P203
	RSPCK ----> P412 - P204

        Pin Connection for EK-RA6M3G
	MISO  ----> P410 - P202
	MOSI  ----> P411 - P203
	RSPCK ----> P412 - P204

        Pin Connection for EK-RA4W1
	MISO  ----> P100 - P110
	MOSI  ----> P101 - P109
	RSPCK ----> P102 - P111


NOTE: User is expected to enter data of size not exceeding 20 bytes.
      The bytes sent for slave should be lesser than the bytes sent for master when using WriteRead operation.
      Operation is not guaranteed for any user input value other than integer,char(i.e. float, special char) through RTT.
