/***********************************************************************************************************************
* 
* Copyright [2020] Renesas Electronics Corporation and/or its affiliates.  All Rights Reserved.
*
* This software is supplied by Renesas Electronics America Inc. and may only be used with products of Renesas Electronics Corp.
* and its affiliates (“Renesas”).  No other uses are authorized.  This software is protected under all applicable laws, 
* including copyright laws.
* Renesas reserves the right to change or discontinue this software.
* THE SOFTWARE IS DELIVERED TO YOU “AS IS,” AND RENESAS MAKES NO REPRESENTATIONS OR WARRANTIES, AND TO THE FULLEST EXTENT 
* PERMISSIBLE UNDER APPLICABLE LAW,DISCLAIMS ALL WARRANTIES, WHETHER EXPLICITLY OR IMPLICITLY, INCLUDING WARRANTIES OF 
* MERCHANTABILITY, FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE, AND NONINFRINGEMENT, WITH RESPECT TO THE SOFTWARE.  TO THE MAXIMUM 
* EXTENT PERMITTED BY LAW, IN NO EVENT WILL RENESAS BE LIABLE TO YOU IN CONNECTION WITH THE SOFTWARE (OR ANY PERSON 
* OR ENTITY CLAIMING RIGHTS DERIVED FROM YOU) FOR ANY LOSS, DAMAGES, OR CLAIMS WHATSOEVER, INCLUDING, WITHOUT LIMITATION, 
* ANY DIRECT, CONSEQUENTIAL, SPECIAL, INDIRECT, PUNITIVE, OR INCIDENTAL DAMAGES;
* ANY LOST PROFITS, OTHER ECONOMIC DAMAGE, PROPERTY DAMAGE, OR PERSONAL INJURY; AND EVEN IF RENESAS HAS BEEN ADVISED OF 
* THE POSSIBILITY OF SUCH LOSS,DAMAGES, CLAIMS OR COSTS.
* 
**********************************************************************************************************************/

1. Project Overview:

        This project demonstrates the basic functionality of NetX Duo SNTP client with Ethernet driver on Renesas 
        RA MCUs using Renesas FSP NetX Duo stack with Azure RTOS. The EP uses mcu_internal RTC for system time and 
        the DHCP client to get the IP address from the DHCP server. On successful receiving of IP address from DHCP 
        server, the success status and Client IP address are displayed on Jlink RTTViewer. SNTP Client is created 
        and SNTP server URL's IP address is resolved through DNS stack functions. SNTP client requests server to 
        provide network time stamp upadtes from server. Upon successful time stamp receive from server, MCU internal 
        RTC timestamp is read and compared with this timestamp and the RTC time stamp is updated if there is difference 
        with received timestamp. Error and info messages will be printed on Jlink RTTViewer.

2. Hardware Requirement:

	i. 1x micro usb cable.
       ii. 2x Ethernet/LAN cable(Ethernet Cable CAT5/6).
      iii. 1x Ethernet Switch to connect to the router or LAN(connected to Internet).

3. Hardware Connections:
 	Supported Board EK_RA6M3, EK_RA6M4 and EK_RA6M5:		
	i. Connect EK_RA6M3 board(J10)/ EK_RA6M4 board(J10)/ EK_RA6M5 board(J10) to Host machine using micro USB cable.
       ii. Connect LAN cable to the Ethernet Port of EK-RA6M3 and other end to the Ethernet Port on the switch 
           or Router. Switch connecting to the router or router should have access to the internet.
	
﻿
1) Segger RTT block address may needed to download and observe EP operation using a hex file with RTT-Viewer.
   RTT Block address for hex file committed in repository are as follows:
   a. e2studio: 0x20001560
   b. Keil: Not Available 
   c. IAR: Not Available
 
2) If an EP is modified, compiled, and downloaded please find the block address (for the variable in RAM called _SEGGER_RTT) 
   in .map file generated in the build configuration folder (Debug/Release).
