/***********************************************************************************************************************
* 
* Copyright [2020] Renesas Electronics Corporation and/or its affiliates.  All Rights Reserved.
*
* This software is supplied by Renesas Electronics America Inc. and may only be used with products of Renesas Electronics Corp.
* and its affiliates (“Renesas”).  No other uses are authorized.  This software is protected under all applicable laws, 
* including copyright laws.
* Renesas reserves the right to change or discontinue this software.
* THE SOFTWARE IS DELIVERED TO YOU “AS IS,” AND RENESAS MAKES NO REPRESENTATIONS OR WARRANTIES, AND TO THE FULLEST EXTENT 
* PERMISSIBLE UNDER APPLICABLE LAW,DISCLAIMS ALL WARRANTIES, WHETHER EXPLICITLY OR IMPLICITLY, INCLUDING WARRANTIES OF 
* MERCHANTABILITY, FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE, AND NONINFRINGEMENT, WITH RESPECT TO THE SOFTWARE.  TO THE MAXIMUM 
* EXTENT PERMITTED BY LAW, IN NO EVENT WILL RENESAS BE LIABLE TO YOU IN CONNECTION WITH THE SOFTWARE (OR ANY PERSON 
* OR ENTITY CLAIMING RIGHTS DERIVED FROM YOU) FOR ANY LOSS, DAMAGES, OR CLAIMS WHATSOEVER, INCLUDING, WITHOUT LIMITATION, 
* ANY DIRECT, CONSEQUENTIAL, SPECIAL, INDIRECT, PUNITIVE, OR INCIDENTAL DAMAGES;
* ANY LOST PROFITS, OTHER ECONOMIC DAMAGE, PROPERTY DAMAGE, OR PERSONAL INJURY; AND EVEN IF RENESAS HAS BEEN ADVISED OF 
* THE POSSIBILITY OF SUCH LOSS,DAMAGES, CLAIMS OR COSTS.
* 
**********************************************************************************************************************/

1. Project Overview:

	This project demonstrates the basic functionality of Netx Duo DHCPv6 client with an ethernet driver on Renesas 
        RA MCUs based on Renesas FSP using AzureRTOS. DHCP Client is created and started. On successful receiving of 
        IP address from DHCPv6 server, It pings the server to verify the received IP address. On successful completion, 
        the success status and IP address are displayed on the RTT viewer. Error and info messages will be printed on JlinkRTTViewer.
  	
2. Hardware Requirement:

	i. 1x micro usb cable.
       ii. 2x Ethernet/LAN cable(Ethernet Cable CAT5/6).
      iii. 1x Ethernet Switch.

3. Hardware Connections:
 	Supported Board EK_RA6M3/EK_RA6M4/EK_RA6M5:		
	i. Connect RA board to Host machine using micro usb cable.
       ii. connect LAN cable on RA board at ethernet port and other end connect to ethernet switch/router. 
	
