/***********************************************************************************************************************
* 
* Copyright [2020] Renesas Electronics Corporation and/or its affiliates.  All Rights Reserved.
*
* This software is supplied by Renesas Electronics America Inc. and may only be used with products of Renesas Electronics Corp.
* and its affiliates (“Renesas”).  No other uses are authorized.  This software is protected under all applicable laws, 
* including copyright laws.
* Renesas reserves the right to change or discontinue this software.
* THE SOFTWARE IS DELIVERED TO YOU “AS IS,” AND RENESAS MAKES NO REPRESENTATIONS OR WARRANTIES, AND TO THE FULLEST EXTENT 
* PERMISSIBLE UNDER APPLICABLE LAW,DISCLAIMS ALL WARRANTIES, WHETHER EXPLICITLY OR IMPLICITLY, INCLUDING WARRANTIES OF 
* MERCHANTABILITY, FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE, AND NONINFRINGEMENT, WITH RESPECT TO THE SOFTWARE.  TO THE MAXIMUM 
* EXTENT PERMITTED BY LAW, IN NO EVENT WILL RENESAS BE LIABLE TO YOU IN CONNECTION WITH THE SOFTWARE (OR ANY PERSON 
* OR ENTITY CLAIMING RIGHTS DERIVED FROM YOU) FOR ANY LOSS, DAMAGES, OR CLAIMS WHATSOEVER, INCLUDING, WITHOUT LIMITATION, 
* ANY DIRECT, CONSEQUENTIAL, SPECIAL, INDIRECT, PUNITIVE, OR INCIDENTAL DAMAGES;
* ANY LOST PROFITS, OTHER ECONOMIC DAMAGE, PROPERTY DAMAGE, OR PERSONAL INJURY; AND EVEN IF RENESAS HAS BEEN ADVISED OF 
* THE POSSIBILITY OF SUCH LOSS,DAMAGES, CLAIMS OR COSTS.
* 
**********************************************************************************************************************/

1. Project Overview:

	This project demonstrates the basic functionality of Netx Duo FTP Client with an ethernet driver on Renesas 
        RA MCUs based on Renesas FSP using AzureRTOS. In this example project FTP client is configured to establish the 
	connection with FTP server. The FTP client will perform read and write operation, on to the currently opened
	file on the FTP server in host machine. The status message and other relevant data will be displayed on Jlink 
	RTT viewer. Error and info messages will be printed on JlinkRTTViewer.
  	
2. Hardware Requirement:

	i. 1x micro usb cable.
       ii. 1x Ethernet/LAN cable(Ethernet Cable CAT5/6).

3. Hardware Connections:
 	Supported Board EK_RA6M3, EK_RA6M4, EK_RA6M5:		
	i. Connect RA board to Host machine using micro usb cable.
       ii. Connect LAN cable on RA board at ethernet port and other end connect to ethernet switch. 
	
4. Software requirements:
 	i.  User need to run FTP Server preferably on windows or linux machine.


Note: 	1)Current ip addresses are provided according to our test environment. User has to change the IP addresses in ip instance
	according to their network configuration
      property of g_ip0_Netx Duo IP instance -> IPv4 Address as per their network environment.
      FTP server IP : if it's a home/close network user can use 192.168.0.x where x represent any available ip address on network.


	2) Segger RTT block address may needed to download and observe EP operation using a hex file with RTT-Viewer.
	   RTT Block address for hex file committed in repository are as follows:
   a. e2studio: 0x20000b78
   	b. Keil: Not Available 
   	c. IAR: Not Available
 
	3) If an EP is modified, compiled, and downloaded please find the block address (for the variable in RAM called _SEGGER_RTT) 
   	in .map file generated in the build configuration folder (Debug/Release).
