/***********************************************************************************************************************
* 
* Copyright [2020] Renesas Electronics Corporation and/or its affiliates.  All Rights Reserved.
*
* This software is supplied by Renesas Electronics America Inc. and may only be used with products of Renesas Electronics Corp.
* and its affiliates (“Renesas”).  No other uses are authorized.  This software is protected under all applicable laws, 
* including copyright laws.
* Renesas reserves the right to change or discontinue this software.
* THE SOFTWARE IS DELIVERED TO YOU “AS IS,” AND RENESAS MAKES NO REPRESENTATIONS OR WARRANTIES, AND TO THE FULLEST EXTENT 
* PERMISSIBLE UNDER APPLICABLE LAW,DISCLAIMS ALL WARRANTIES, WHETHER EXPLICITLY OR IMPLICITLY, INCLUDING WARRANTIES OF 
* MERCHANTABILITY, FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE, AND NONINFRINGEMENT, WITH RESPECT TO THE SOFTWARE.  TO THE MAXIMUM 
* EXTENT PERMITTED BY LAW, IN NO EVENT WILL RENESAS BE LIABLE TO YOU IN CONNECTION WITH THE SOFTWARE (OR ANY PERSON 
* OR ENTITY CLAIMING RIGHTS DERIVED FROM YOU) FOR ANY LOSS, DAMAGES, OR CLAIMS WHATSOEVER, INCLUDING, WITHOUT LIMITATION, 
* ANY DIRECT, CONSEQUENTIAL, SPECIAL, INDIRECT, PUNITIVE, OR INCIDENTAL DAMAGES;
* ANY LOST PROFITS, OTHER ECONOMIC DAMAGE, PROPERTY DAMAGE, OR PERSONAL INJURY; AND EVEN IF RENESAS HAS BEEN ADVISED OF 
* THE POSSIBILITY OF SUCH LOSS,DAMAGES, CLAIMS OR COSTS.
* 
**********************************************************************************************************************/

1. Project Overview:

	This project demonstrates the basic functionality of Netx Duo SMTP client with an ethernet driver on Renesas 
        RA MCUs based on Renesas FSP using AzureRTOS. The project creates SMTP client and transfer e-mail message
        to local configured SMTP server. Based on user input from RTTViewer, EP Performs:
        1. Enter 1 to send email message to the server.
        2. Enter 2 to view Pre-configured email message.
        On successful completion, the success status are displayed on the RTT viewer. Error and info messages will be 
        printed on JlinkRTTViewer.
  	
2. Hardware Requirement:

	i. 1x micro usb cable.
       ii. 2x Ethernet/LAN cable(Ethernet Cable CAT5/6).
      iii. 1x Ethernet Switch.

3. Hardware Connections:
 	Supported Board EK_RA6M3, EK_RA6M4 and EK_RA6M5:		
	i. Connect RA board to Host machine using micro usb cable.
       ii. Connect LAN cable on RA board at ethernet port and other end connect to ethernet switch.
           
4. Software requirements:
       i.  User need to install and run Argo SoftMail server. For details please refer NetX_smtp_client_notes.md file.

Note : Users need to configure the server ip address and client ip address in the configuration property of g_smtp_client0 Netx Duo SMTP Client -> Server IPv4 Address and
       the client ip address in configurator property of g_ip0_Netx Duo IP instance -> IPv4 Address as per their network environment.
       For e.g 
       Client IP : if its an home network user can use 192.168.0.x where x represent any available ip address on network.    
       Server IP : For Server ip use ip of the pc in which smtp mail server is configured in the same network environment.
 
	
﻿
1) Segger RTT block address may needed to download and observe EP operation using a hex file with RTT-Viewer.
   RTT Block address for hex file committed in repository are as follows:
   a. e2studio: 0x20000d78
   b. Keil: Not Available 
   c. IAR: Not Available
 
2) If an EP is modified, compiled, and downloaded please find the block address (for the variable in RAM called _SEGGER_RTT) 
   in .map file generated in the build configuration folder (Debug/Release).
