/***********************************************************************************************************************
* Copyright [2020] Renesas Electronics Corporation and/or its affiliates.  All Rights Reserved.

*
 This software is supplied by Renesas Electronics America Inc. and may only be used with products of Renesas Electronics Corp.

* and its affiliates (“Renesas”).  No other uses are authorized.  This software is protected under all applicable laws, 

* including copyright laws.

* Renesas reserves the right to change or discontinue this software.

* THE SOFTWARE IS DELIVERED TO YOU “AS IS,” AND RENESAS MAKES NO REPRESENTATIONS OR WARRANTIES, AND TO THE FULLEST EXTENT 

* PERMISSIBLE UNDER APPLICABLE LAW,DISCLAIMS ALL WARRANTIES, WHETHER EXPLICITLY OR IMPLICITLY, INCLUDING WARRANTIES OF 

* MERCHANTABILITY, FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE, AND NONINFRINGEMENT, WITH RESPECT TO THE SOFTWARE.  TO THE MAXIMUM 

* EXTENT PERMITTED BY LAW, IN NO EVENT WILL RENESAS BE LIABLE TO YOU IN CONNECTION WITH THE SOFTWARE (OR ANY PERSON 

* OR ENTITY CLAIMING RIGHTS DERIVED FROM YOU) FOR ANY LOSS, DAMAGES, OR CLAIMS WHATSOEVER, INCLUDING, WITHOUT LIMITATION, 

* ANY DIRECT, CONSEQUENTIAL, SPECIAL, INDIRECT, PUNITIVE, OR INCIDENTAL DAMAGES;

* ANY LOST PROFITS, OTHER ECONOMIC DAMAGE, PROPERTY DAMAGE, OR PERSONAL INJURY; AND EVEN IF RENESAS HAS BEEN ADVISED OF 

* THE POSSIBILITY OF SUCH LOSS,DAMAGES, CLAIMS OR COSTS.

* **********************************************************************************************************************/



1. Project Overview:

        This Example Project demonstrates the functionality of OPAMP module.

        Analog voltage is provided through DAC module which is taken from user through JLINK RTT viewer.

        OPAMP processing is triggered through software once user input DAC value in the range of 0 to 4095.

        OPAMP output is fed to ADC in turn the result is displayed on RTTViewer.



2. Hardware settings for the project:

        Hardware connections:

        
RA2A1-EK:

        1) P502(J3)   --> P015(J2)

        2) VREFHO(J2) --> AVCCO(J2) and VREFLO(J2) --> AVSSO(J2)

        3) VREFL(J3)  --> GND


        
	RA4M1-EK:

        1) P014(DAC0) --> P000(both on J2)

        2) P002(J4)   --> Both P001(J2) and P003(J2)

	RA4W1-EK:
	1) P014(DAC0 (CN8-32)) --> P011(OPAMP+ (CN8-37))
	2) Measure output at P004(OPAMPO (CN8-40)) using multimeter.



NOTE:
 1. a) For RA4W1-EK, Remove R14 and R17 and install R20 and R21.
    b) Measure the output at OPAMP output pin(P004) using multimeter
.
 2. User is expected to enter data of size not exceeding above 15 bytes.

 3. Operation is not guaranteed for any user input value other than integer(i.e. float, char, special char) through Jlik RTTviewer.

