/***********************************************************************************************************************
* Copyright [2019] Renesas Electronics Corporation and/or its affiliates.  All Rights Reserved.
*
* This software is supplied by Renesas Electronics America Inc. and may only be used with products of Renesas Electronics Corp.
* and its affiliates (“Renesas”).  No other uses are authorized.  This software is protected under all applicable laws, 
* including copyright laws.
* Renesas reserves the right to change or discontinue this software.
* THE SOFTWARE IS DELIVERED TO YOU “AS IS,” AND RENESAS MAKES NO REPRESENTATIONS OR WARRANTIES, AND TO THE FULLEST EXTENT 
* PERMISSIBLE UNDER APPLICABLE LAW,DISCLAIMS ALL WARRANTIES, WHETHER EXPLICITLY OR IMPLICITLY, INCLUDING WARRANTIES OF 
* MERCHANTABILITY, FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE, AND NONINFRINGEMENT, WITH RESPECT TO THE SOFTWARE.  TO THE MAXIMUM 
* EXTENT PERMITTED BY LAW, IN NO EVENT WILL RENESAS BE LIABLE TO YOU IN CONNECTION WITH THE SOFTWARE (OR ANY PERSON 
* OR ENTITY CLAIMING RIGHTS DERIVED FROM YOU) FOR ANY LOSS, DAMAGES, OR CLAIMS WHATSOEVER, INCLUDING, WITHOUT LIMITATION, 
* ANY DIRECT, CONSEQUENTIAL, SPECIAL, INDIRECT, PUNITIVE, OR INCIDENTAL DAMAGES;
* ANY LOST PROFITS, OTHER ECONOMIC DAMAGE, PROPERTY DAMAGE, OR PERSONAL INJURY; AND EVEN IF RENESAS HAS BEEN ADVISED OF 
* THE POSSIBILITY OF SUCH LOSS,DAMAGES, CLAIMS OR COSTS.
* **********************************************************************************************************************/

1. Project Overview:
	The example project demonstrates the typical use of the RTC HAL module APIs. 
	The project initializes the RTC module and allows the user to set RTC Calendar time and Calendar alarm.
	User can enable periodic interrupt and can also view the current RTC calendar time.
        On enabling periodic interrupt, on-board LED toggles every 1 second and on occurrence of Calendar alarm. LED is turned ON.
	
NOTE:
   1. User is expected to enter Time values to set Calendar time and Calendar alarm in 24-hours format.
        Sample Input: 23:10:2019 16:14:55 (DD:MM:YYYY HH:MM:SS)
   2. Time related C library functions are used for demonstration purpose in this Example project. So, for now this EP 
      will work only in debugger environment. If you flash the code and connect the RTT alone, 
      example project will not produce any output
   3. User is expected to enter data of size not exceeding above 15 bytes.
   4. Operation is not guaranteed for any user input value other than integer,char(i.e. float, special char) through RTT.